Senior QA Engineer with over 7 years of experience in API and automation testing, including mobile and performance testing. Certified in ISTQB Foundation, ISTQB Agile Tester, and Professional Scrum Master I, focusing on technical excellence and quality results.

My experience in the startup environment has provided me with a unique perspective on agility, innovation, and problem-solving.

Capable of leading teams, coaching other testers, and adapting to changing environments in agile teams using Scrum, I contribute to seamless collaboration and effective teamwork with international colleagues while being fluent in English.

### **SKILLS**

Playwright • Typescript • Selenium • PostgreSQL • Postman • Kibana • Gitlab • Snowflake • AWS • Kafka • Python • Java • Go • Cucumber • Gherkin • K6 • Jmeter • Jira • Asana

LANGUAGES: English B2 - upper intermediate

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Tribal Credit, Senior QA Engineer** — February 2022-present

Startup that provides credit cards for companies. Agile team with Scrum.

- Automation testing using Playwright and TypeScript
- API testing and performance testing
- Lead a team that tests the new system Tribal 2.0, focused on customers from Chile, Colombia, Peru and Brazil.
- Lead a team that migrates customers from Tribal 1.0 to Tribal 2.0 system.

### **Tranzact, Senior Software QA Engineer** — July 2021-January 2022

Insurance sales to US customers. Agile team with Scrum.

- Automation testing using Java and Python
- API testing
- Lead a team, focused on testing a new campaign related to a new insurance product

## **Everis Perú SAC, Software Test Engineer** — January 2019-June 2021

Outsourcing for Interbank, peruvian bank. Agile team with Scrum.

- Automation testing using Selenium, Java, Serenity BDD, cucumber
- Functional testing for credits and loans, checking balances and accountability amounts
- Lead a team, focused on new features indicated by the regulation supervisor in Peru

#### Canvia, Software Quality Analyst — April 2017- December 2018

Outsourcing for Interbank, peruvian bank. Agile team with Scrum.

- Automation testing using Selenium and Java
- Functional testing for savings accounts, transfers and credit cards. checking balances and accountability amounts

### GMD SA, QA Analyst — September 2016- March 2017

Outsourcing for Interbank, peruvian bank. Team working with traditional project management.

- Functional testing for savings accounts, transfers and credit cards. checking balances and accountability amounts
- Test case and test plan creation, regression testing

### **EDUCATION**

# Universidad Tecnológica del Perú – Lima, Lima

Bachellor in Mecatronics Engineer, December 2012